# Carla Conradie

**UX/UI** Designer



Bē Behance Portfolio

# **About**

UX/UI designer with a background in delivering visual effects work for Hollywood film productions. Extensive experience taking projects from brief to launch, collaborating and connecting with international teams, and finding the right solutions to creative and technical problems.

## **Tools**

Figma
Google Suite
MS Office Suite
Slack
Basic HTML/CSS

## Skills

User interviews
User personas
Wireframing
Mockups/Prototyping
Usability testing
Project Management
Data visualisation
Communication/Team Building
Client management

## Education

#### **Career Foundry**

2023-2024, London Certificate in UI Design with a specialisation in Frontend Development for Designers

#### **McGill University/Sciences Po**

2011-2015, Montréal/Paris B.A. Art History + Political Science with 12 month bilingual exchange program

# Languages

English (fluent) French (fluent) Afrikaans (fluent)

# **Projects**

### Village Childcare App, UX/UI Designer

Career Foundry project case study, April 2024

Designed an app enabling families to connect for childcare needs. Conducted user research, built interactive prototypes with Figma, and responded to usability test results to produce high fidelity UI meeting both iOS and Android guidelines.

### Alacart Meal Planning App, UX/UI Designer

Career Foundry project case study, January - March 2024

Created final mockups for a responsive web app allowing users to save and plan weekly recipes. Using a mobile-first approach, defined user personas before iterating on wireframes, and applying a cohesive style guide to UI elements.

# **Professional Experience**

#### Untold Studios, Associate VFX Producer

February 2024 - present, London

Strategise team priorities, forecast resource needs, and manage client relations for Paramount Pictures feature, in order to maintain smooth delivery of VFX work to agreed budget.

#### One of Us, Associate VFX Producer

March 2022 - February 2024, Paris/London

Upgraded studio's scheduling database in order to better organise and communicate internal delivery targets, increasing efficiencies and client satisfaction for two largest and most complex projects to date, both Netflix features.

### Framestore, VFX Line Producer

October 2019 - March 2022, London

Built and maintained VFX production schedule for various features, troubleshooting technical obstacles and overseeing smooth feedback loop to produce approved images for clients at A24, Warner Bros, and Netflix/StudioCanal.

## **Double Negative**, VFX Line Producer

July 2018 - September 2019, London

Organised day-to-day tasks for team of artists, providing support necessary to meet internal and external delivery milestones for Universal Pictures and Sony/Marvel projects.